Sync:YTET-Vicky8800
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
"dexter" 지난 이야기...
previously on "dexter"...
이것도 그 자식 짓인거 같아?
think this is our guy's work?
냉동트럭 킬러?
The ice-truck killer?
라거타 부서장이 범인의 지능을 깔봐서
Laguerta insulted the real killer's intelligence,
엉뚱한 사람을 쫓는 사이에
그 놈이 되돌아 온거라구요
and now he's getting back at us for
chasing after the wrong guy.
그 투치라는 경비원
It's the guard -- tucci.
살아있는 거 같아요
I think he's alive.
투치가 살아 있다고?
Tucci's alive?
냉동트럭 살인마는 절단 행위를
계속하기 위해 그를 살려두고 있을 겁니다
The ice-truck killer is keeping him
alive to perform amputations.
놈이 메세지를 보내고 있다
He's sending me a message.
나보고 그 곳에 가라는 뜻이다
He wants me to go there.
제발
Please.
놈은, 내가 죽이기를 바라고
이 사람을 남겨둔 것이다
He was left here so I would kill him.
그냥 죽여줘
Just kill me.
난 이 사람을 죽일수 없다
I can't kill this man.
지금 투치를 병원으로
데려가는 중입니다, 살아 있어요
I'm taking tucci over to county alive.
누구한테서 정보를 얻었는지 모르지만, 모건
I don't know who your contacts are, morgan,
자넨 이제 내 눈에 띈 거야
but you are my up-and-comer.
자넨 오늘밤 한 남자의 생명을 구했어
You saved a man's life tonight.
리타를 만나면서 내가 가장 놀란건
The thing that surprises me most about rita is
그녀와 같이 있는게
굉장히 좋다는 점이다
how much I like being with her.
내가 해줄수 있는 일도 있어
There's all sorts of things I can do.
뭐... 뭐하는 거야?
what are you doing?
내가 원하는 거
Whatever I want.
내 새로운 친구는, 내가 자기 선물을 죽이지
않고는 못 배길거라 생각했겠지만, 나는 참아냈다
My new friend thought I wouldn't be able to resist
the kill he left for me,but I did.
난 놈이 바라던 몬스터가 되지 않았다
I'm not the monster he wants me to be.
난 덱스터다
I'm dexter.
Dexter 1x05
난 내가 혼자라고 상상하는게 좋다
완벽한 혼자가 되는것
I like to pretend I'm alone,completely alone
인류가 멸망한 뒤나
흑사병이 퍼진 뒤처럼
maybe post-apocalypse or plague
사람이 아무도 없어서
평범한척 연기할 필요가 없다면
whatever no one left to act normal for
진정한 나를 숨길 필요가 없다면
no need to hide who I really am.
그건 해방일 것이다
It would be freeing.
빌어먹을 사이코처럼
쪼개고 있지 말고 일이나 해
Stop grinning like a fucking psycho and get back to work.
미안해요, 경사
Sorry, sergeant.
내가 들어가서 휘저어놓기 전에
감식반이 증거물수집 끝내길 기다리고 있었죠
I was just waiting for forensics to wrap up
before I tear the bed apart.
혼자인걸 즐기는 사람이
나 뿐인 건 아니다
I'm not the only one who enjoys isolation.
유령같은 내 친구도
이런 장소를 선택했으니 말이다
My shadow companion chose this place well.
여긴 그의 안식처였다
적어도 잠시 동안은
This was his sanctuary,for a while, at least.
이들이 여길 어질러 놓는건
All these people pawing over it seems...
무례하게 느껴진다
disrespectful.
그 역겨운 놈의 혈흔이
나와야 할텐데, 덱스터
Tell me the sick bastard bled on something, dexter.
날카로운 물건 가지고
여기서 며칠을 놀았으니까 말야
He was here for days,playing with sharp objects.
계속 찾아보겠지만 지금까진 깨끗해요
I'll keep looking, but so far this place is spotless
아주 놀라울 정도죠, 찾아낸 혈흔이라곤
그 경비원 것 밖에 없어요
amazingly so.The only blood I
found belongs to the security guard.
경비원은 아직 별 말 없어요?
Has he said anything yet?
투치 씨는 여전히 의식불명이야
Mr. Tucci's still unconscious.
경위님, 올라와 보세요!
Lieutenant, up here!
분명히 뭔가가 나올거야, 찾아내
There's got to be something here. Find it.
그 놈이 유령은 아니잖아
토니 투치가 그 증거고
The guy's not a ghost.
Tony tucci is evidence of that.
왔어, 덱스터
이 혈흔들 사진은 다 찍었지?
Hey, dexter, you get all this blood on camera yet?
잭슨 폴락의 추상화를
찍는거 같았어요
It's like shooting a jackson pollock.
그럼, 잭슨 폴락의 추상화가
증거물 봉투로 들어가겠습니다
Well, your jackson pollock is in the bag.
같이?
Ready?
그래
Okay.
워우, 뭐였지?
Whoa. What was that?
저거 봤어?
Did you see that?
뭘요?
What?
망할놈의 쥐들
Damn rats.
먼지속에 있는 저놈들 세균때문에
우리 모두 히스토플라스마증에 걸릴거야
We're all gonna get histoplasmosis
from all their shit in the dust.
기침하다 피를 토하고
피부엔 혹이나 사마귀, 입안에는 염증
We'll be coughing up blood,skin lesions, mouth sores.
멋지네요
Lovely.
불 좀 꺼주시겠어요?
Can we get the lights, guys?
'서교열'이라고 못들어 봤어?
(쥐,개,고양이 등에 물려서 생기는 병)
You ever heard of rat-bite fever?
마수카!
Masuka
그 빌어먹을 쥐 얘기, 내가 뭐랬지?
what'd I say about the fucking rats?
지금까지 아무것도 못 찾았고
앞으로도 아무것도 못찼을거야
You haven't found anything,won't find anything.
완전 허탕이야, 그치?
This is a bust, right?
니 말 그대로야
In so many words.
그럼, 투치가 깨어날 때 까지
난 허송세월 해야돼잖아
Which means I'm just jerking off till tucci wakes up.
그럼 좀 쉬어
넌 줄곧 이 사건에만 매달려 왔잖아
So take a break.You've been working this thing 24-7.
아님 여전히
사생활 가지는 걸 피하는거야?
Or are you still avoiding a personal life?
오, 엿 먹어
Oh, fuck you.
하지만 맞아
일에 몰두하는게 더 좋으니까
And, yeah, I'm better off just focusing on the job.
다 됐습니다
Thanks, guys.
일과 사생활을 반드시
구분할 필요는 없어
It doesn't have to be either/or.
그래서 요즘 연애에 빠지셨나
Maybe not for you.
내가 누군가를 찾을 수 있다면
너도 할 수 있어, 맞지?
If I found someone,so can you, right?
맞아, 문제는 어떻게 붙잡아 두느냐지
Yeah, the trouble is keeping them.
내말이 그 말이다
Tell me about it.
옐리나?
Yelina?
무슨 일 있어요?
Are you okay?
죄송해요, 전 괜찮아요
I'm sorry. I'm fine.
어네스토는 아직 안 왔어요?
Ernesto hasn't arrived?
분명 어네스토는 곧 올거예요
I'm sure he'll be here soon.
아뇨
No.
코요테가 돈을
더 달라고 했는데 줄 돈이 없었어요
The coyote wanted more money,and I didn't have it.
코요테요?
Coyote?
어네스토를 데려다 달라고
돈을 준 사람 말이죠?
You mean the man you paid to bring him here?
그 사람이 어네스토를
쿠바로 돌려 보낸댔어요
He said he sent ernesto back to cuba.
그렇게 말한지가 일주일 전인데
But that was a week ago,
아직 카데나스에선 아무도
어네스토 소식을 몰라요
and no one in c*rdenas has heard from ernesto.
옐리나, 그 코요테랑
어떻게 연락을 주고 받아요?
Yelina, how did you contact this coyote?
그사람 번호는 이건데
더이상 연락이 안돼요
...this was his number,but it's not working anymore.
공원에 그 사람 줄 돈을
갖다 두기로 했었어요
I was supposed to leave him money in a park.
있잖아요, 내 남자친구가
경찰에서 일해요
Listen, my boyfriend works for the police.
그 사람이... / 안돼, 안돼요
I'm sure he --no, no, no.
경찰에 알릴 순 없어요
We can't go to the police.
그 코요테가 경찰에 알리면
쿠바에 있는 가족을 해칠거랬어요
He said he'd hurt my family in cuba if we go to the police.
괜찮을거예요
No, it's okay.
괜찮아요
It's okay.
덱스터는 뭘 해야할지 알 거예요
Dexter will know what to do.
옐리나를 보면 마음이 안됐어
I feel just terrible for her.
그 남자가 여기 오면
둘이 결혼하기로 했었대
And they were supposed to be married after he got here.
밀입국자 문제를 다루는 부서에
내가 아는 사람이 있어
I do know someone in the department
who deals with immigration issues.
그 사람한테 말해 볼수도 있어
I can talk to him.
그래주면 정말 고마울거야, 덱스
That's really kind of you, dex.
자기 약혼자가 죽었는지 살았는지
모른다는게 어떤건지 상상이나 돼?
I mean, can you imagine not knowing
if your fiance is dead or alive?
오우, 안돼지
Uh, no.
옐리나는 매일밤 퇴근 후에
길건너 해변에 가
Every night after work yelina goes
across the street,to the beach.
약혼자가 물에서 걸어나오길 바라는듯이
멍하니 바다만 바라보고 있던 걸
I've seen her there,just staring out at the water,
willing him to walk out of it.
당신 뭔가를
그렇게 애타게 바란 적 있어?
Have you ever longed for anything like that?
리타는 내게 뭔가를 바라고 있다
She wants something from me.
그 블로우잡(입 봉사)이후로, 리타는
우리가 다음단계로 넘어갔다고 생각한다
Ever since the blow job,
she assumes we've taken it to the next level.
아직 모르고 있는 것이다
내게 다음 단계란 없다는 것을
She doesn't know yet,I don't have a next level.
내가 꼬마였을 때
아타리 게임기가 죽도록 갖고 싶었어
Well, when I was a kid,I would have killed for an atari.
이렇게 하는거
You know?
그래픽이 조잡해서 당신 아들
코디도 웃겠지만 그 당시에는 정말...
Cody would laugh at the graphics now, but back then, man...
첫 섹스를 하고 나면 언제나 이렇게 된다
It always comes to this once sex is introduced.
더이상 잡담으로는 모면할수가 없다
Small talk no longer cuts it.
결국 그녀는 날 연구대상이라고 부르며
Eventually she'll call me a science project
집에도 들이지 않을 것이다
and slam the door in my face.
그럼 언제쯤 깨어날 거 같은데요?
But when do you think he'll wake up?
네, 한시간 전에도 전화했었어요
Yeah, I did call an hour ago,but there's a killer out there
지금 거리엔 창녀와 경비원을
노리는 살인마가 있다구요
that's into whores and security guards,
다음번엔 분명 간호사를 노릴걸요
but I'll bet nurses are next.
와, 마이애미 경찰언니시네
Yo, check you,all "mpd blue."
샨다, 여긴 어쩐 일이야?
Shanda,what are you doing here?
냉동트럭 살인마에 대한
다른 단서라도 있는 거야?
You have another lead on the ice-truck killer?
그 역겨운 새끼보다
더 큰 걱정거리가 있어
Man, I got bigger worries than that sick shit.
이젠, 나도 경찰 빽 좀 써보자, 응?
Now, I got me a girl on the inside, right?
니네 포주 꺼내달라는 소리라면
그건 안돼
I'm not springing your pimp,if that's what you're after.
아 젠장, 아냐
Oh, hell, no.
실은 망할놈의 우리 집 주인 얘기야
But my landlord's another fucking story --
날 내 집에서 쫓아내려고 해
trying to kick me out of my home.
아무 이유도 없이 그래
창녀싫다고 위선이나 떠는 씨발새끼!
He got no cause,except he's a born-again
hypocrite mother fucker.
그럼, 가서 집주인이랑 얘기해달라고?
Yeah, and you want me to talk to him?
아니, 밀가루 반죽같이 허연 그 새끼
얼굴을 뭉개줬음 좋겠어 / 모건
No, I want you to beat in his pasty, white face.
Morgan.
증거물들 중에서 이게 나왔어
Found this in evidence.
마수카가 이걸 검사하려는 중이었어
Masuka was gonna grease it through.
담배 꽁초가 나왔어요?
A cigarette butt?
세상에, 그거면 DNA를 찾아낼수 있어요
잘하면 지문까지두요
Jesus, we could pull dna off of that, or even a print.
그래, 아마 니 지문이 나올거야
Except it would be your print.
니가 범죄현장에서 담배 피웠잖아
You were smoking on a crime scene.
범죄현장은 아니었어요
멀리 떨어진 공원 끝자락 쯤일거에요
Not on the crime scene --like on the way-far end of the park.
그 전 지역이 다 범죄현장이야
The whole area's a crime scene.
지금 쯤이면 그 정돈 알아야지
매춘 단속 하다온게 무슨 벼슬이냐
You should know that by now.
우선 빌어먹을 흥분부터 좀
가라앉히세요, 오빠
Maybe you ought to just calm the hell down, my brother.
얘는 또 뭐야?
Who the fuck is that?
그만 좀 해, 샨다
Give it a rest, shanda.
가서 쓸모있는 일 좀해, 모건
Morgan,go do something useful.
가서 그 경비원 깨어날때까지
지키고 앉아 있어
Go sit on that security guard until he wakes up.
나 없이 혼자서는
그 사람하고 얘기하지 말고
And do not talk to him without me.
내말 믿어, 그런 일 당한게
자네 가정부가 처음은 아니야
Believe me --your maid is not the first one to get screwed.
내 가정부는 아니에요
No, she's a maid.
She's not my maid.
그럼 그 밖에 다른 쿠바 밀입국자들이
사라졌다는 얘기는 못 들었구요?
So, have you heard of any other
cuban immigrants disappearing?
몇 명 있지
가난한 인간들
A few.The poor bastards.
평생 일해서 모은 돈으로
They spend their life savings,
어선창에 빽빽히 끼여서
90마일을 토하면서 마이애미까지 와서
get stuffed into a fishhold,puke the whole 90 miles to miami.
그리고는 생각하지
"난 이제 미국인이야, 난 자유야."
Then they get here, thinking,"I'm an american. I'm free."
망할놈의 코요테만 없다면 그렇겠지
Except the damn coyote...
가족들이 돈을 가져올 때 까지는
밀입국자들을 풀어 주지 않아
he won't let them go till his family comes up
with a surprise release fee.
결국 돈을 못내면 / 사라지는군요
If they can't pay...they disappear.
자유를 찾와 왔다가 인생 종치는 거지
Freedom's just another word for one more way to get fucked.
누군가가 아주 나쁜짓을
하고 있는거 같다
Sounds like someone's doing something very bad.
용의자는 있나요?
You have any suspects?
그럼, 네다섯 명 있는데
대부분 자기네 쿠바 사람이야
Sure, four or five, mostly cubans themselves,
하지만 증거가 부족해서
유죄판결은 고사하고 영장도 못받고 있어
but not enough evidence for a conviction or even a warrant.
영장이 신청됐었으니
If warrants were applied for,
데이터베이스에 그놈들 이름이 있을거다
their names will be in the database.
이봐, 친구
Look, buddy...
자네가 가정부를 돕고 싶은건 알겠지만
I know you want to help out your maid,
할수 있는 일은 아무것도 없어
but there ain't a hell of a lot you can do.
깜짝 놀라게 될걸요
You'd be surprised.
호르헤 카스티요
Jorge castillo --
경찰 용의자 리스트에서 세 번째지만
number 3 on the department's list of suspects
옐리나가 돈을 놔두기로 했던
공원에서 그나마 가까이 있는 유일한 자다
but the only one even remotely close to the park
where yelina was supposed to drop the money.
경찰은 증거부족으로 영장을 못받아서
여기를 수색할수 없겠지만
They never got enough evidence for a search warrant
내가 이 자를 지켜보는 데에는
법원의 허락이 필요없다
but I don't need permission to keep an eye on this guy.
이웃도 없고 보행자도 없다
가능성이 있다
No neighbors,no foot traffic --it's promising.
좋은 장소다
인신 매매나...더 나쁜 짓을 하기엔
A good place for human trafficking...or worse.
잠깐만요
Excuse me.
여긴 사유지인데요
Private yard.
혹시 69년형 콜벳 스팅레이용
헤드라이트를 갖고 계신가해서 왔습니다
I'm just praying you have a '69 stingray
headlight somewhere in here.
아, 전 데이브 커틀러입니다
Uh, dave cutler.
호르헤 카스티요예요
Jorge castillo.
미안하지만, 저한텐 없어요
I'm sorry, but I don'T.
제 스팅레이의 복원이
거의 완료 됐거든요, 정말 멋진 차죠
Man, my restoration's almost done.
She's a beauty.
커틀러씨, 저는 개인에게는 판매를 안합니다
I don't do individual sales,mr. Cutler,
대신 제가 거래하고 있는
콜벳 샵을 알려드릴 수는 있어요
but I can give you the name of a corvette shop I deal with.
제가 여길 둘러볼수 있으면
참 좋겠는데요
I'll be happy to look around myself.
오해는 마시구요
여길 둘러보게 해 드리자면
No offense, man,but I can't take my phone orders
제가 전화 주문을 받을 수가 없어서요
if I'm watching over my merchandise.
여기 전체를 혼자 경영하세요?
You run this whole place alone?
네, 비용을 줄일 수 있으니까요
Yeah, it keeps my costs down.
여기까지 찾아오셨는데 죄송하군요
Hey, I'm sorry you made the trip out here.
있잖아요?
You know what?
타마락에 있는 웩슬러네 샵으로 가보세요
저와 거래하는 콜벳샵이에요
Try wexler's,out in tamarac.
That's my vette guy.
그러죠
Yeah.
자기 사업을 하시니 좋겠어요
Must be nice being your own boss --
바다에 가고 싶으면 마음대로 갈수 있고
get out in the water whenever you want.
당신 열쇠고리에 있는 낚시찌를 봤거든요
저도 그런 거 하나 사야겠어요
I saw that floater on your key chain.
I got to get one of those.
작년엔 배에 있다가 열쇠를
두번이나 바다에 빠뜨렸어요
Lost my keys overboard twice in the past year.
전 낚시를 가끔 해요, 32피트짜리
콘셉트(3M의 낚시줄)를 써요, 당신은요?
I do a little fishing.I got a 32-foot concept.
What about you?
낚시구멍이 있는 노젓는 배가 있어요
I got a rowboat with a hole in it.
유명한 메이커 제품을 쓰면
고기가 알아서 찾아올 것이다
A lo major los pescados te encuentran.
전 스페인어 못합니다
I don't speak spanish, sir.
미안해요, 쿠바 분으로 착각했네요
Sorry.I just assumed you were cuban.
미국인이죠, 당신처럼
American, pal,just like you.
나처럼이라...
Just like me.
지금 강한 진정제를 투여한 상태예요
그럴만도 하지 않나요
He's on heavy sedatives at the moment.
I think he deserves them.
깨어날 때까지 기다릴께요
I'll wait.
이봐요
Hey.
투치 씨
Mr. Tucci.
토니
Tony.
내가 그 망할자식을 잡을께요
I'm gonna find this cocksucker.
맹세해요
I swear.
난 자동차에 대한 미국의 집착을 이해할 수 없다
I don't understand america's obsession with cars.
리타와 두 아이를 자동차에 쑤셔넣고
여행길을 떠나는게 상상이 된다
I can just imagine squeezing rita and the kids
into that thing and hitting the open road --
비좁은 1/4의 공간, 공중 화장실
대화말곤 할께 없는 시간들...
cramped quarters,public bathrooms,
hours of nothing but conversation.
어떤 이에겐 어메리칸 드림,
내겐 악몽이다
It's someone's american dream -- my nightmare.
카스티요가 밀입국자들을
가둬두는 장소가 분명하다
This must be where castillo locks them up.
하지만, 그가 돈을 못낸 밀입국자들을
죽인다면, 여기서 하진 않을거다
But if he's killing them when they can't pay
he's not doing it here.
그럼 그들은 어디에 있는걸까?
So where are they?
덱스터 모건입니다
Dexter morgan.
나 제라드야
Gerard here.
사우스비치 시체공시소에 떠밀려온
시체가 있어, 자네 가정부 약혼자 같아
There's a floater down in south beach morgue.
Could be a match for your maid's fianc?
내 가정부 아니에요
She's a maid.
내 가정부가 아니...
그녀를 거기 데려가도 괜찮아요?
She's not my --is it all right if I bring her down?
빠를수록 좋지
The sooner, the better.
그럼 알았어요, 고마워요
좋은 하루 보내요
Okay, then. Thanks.Have a good day.
오늘 밤 살사룸이야
Tonight at the salsa room.
나 봉급 오른거 축하하는데 니가 참석해야지
You got to help me celebrate my pay-grade bump.
실은, 개인적으로 연구할게 좀 있어서
오늘밤은 일할 거예요
Actually, I have a personal project I'm working on tonight.
다음으로 미뤄, 내가 살테니까
Blow it off.I'm buying.
앤젤, 목격자 제보 선별작업은 한거야?
Angel, do you have that list of prioritized witnesses?
800건이나 되는 익명제보를
다 살펴볼순 없잖아
I can't deal with 800 anonymous tips.
하는 중이에요
I'm working on it.
그럼, 수다는 그만 떨고
봉급 오른 값 좀 하는게 어때?
Well, how about you stop talking and earn your bump?
섹시해
Sexy.
오늘밤에 나 기다리게 하지마, 친구
Don't leave me hanging tonight, bro.
우리 둘만 가는거야
It's you and me.
내가 어쨌길래
우리가 이리 친하다고 생각하는지 모르겠다
I wonder what I did to make him think we're so close.
리타가 달라진 것도 같은 이유인가?
I wonder if it'd work on rita.
아까 전화했었던 덱스터 모건입니다
Dexter morgan --I called earlier.
아 맞아요, 그 바다에 떠오른 시체
Oh, right, yeah, about the floater.
네
Yeah.
이봐, 제리 이 분들
뒤로 좀 안내해 줄래?
Hey, jerry, can you take these guys around back?
나도 갈까?
Should I?
아냐, 내가 같이 갈께
Nah,I'll go with her.
옐리나가 기댈 데가 필요할테니까
She might need a shoulder.
내가 기댈 만한 놈이 아니란걸
리타가 알아챘다
She senses I'm not a shoulder.
나쁜 징조다, 그녀가 눈치채가고 있다
Bad sign -- she's catching on.
얼마나 멍청하길래 90마일이나 되는 바다를
튜브를 타고 건널 생각을 했는지 모르겠어요
I don't know what kind of idiot thinks an inner tube
is gonna get him over 90 miles of open ocean.
내 견해로는, 다윈의
적자생존설이 작용한 거예요
If you ask me, man,it's darwin's theory at work.
사랑은 분명 저런 모습일 것이다
That must be what love looks like.
둔감한 것도 이점은 있다...
The inability to feel has its advantages...
..가끔은
...sometimes.
안녕 덱스터
Hey, dexter.
안녕 민디
Hey, mindy.
내가 도와줄까?
Do you need any help?
아니
No.
근데, 너 봄철 무도회에 갈 거니?
So, are you gonna go to the spring formal?
내가 왜 그런데 가겠냐?
Why would I want to do that?
저 애는 니가 파트너 신청을
해주길 바라는 거야, 덱스터
She wanted you to ask her to the dance, dexter.
그런 말은 안하던데요
That's not what she said.
음, 넌 여자들의 신호를 배워야돼
Well, you have to learn their signals.
전 여자애들 별로 신경 안쓰는 걸요
Yeah, well, I don't really care about girls.
오우
Oh.
그냥 전.. 혼자있는게 좋아요
I just like being alone.
그치만 평범한 사람들 대부분은 안그렇다
But most normal people don't
그리고 넌 평범하게 보여야 돼
and it's important that you seem normal.
전 평범하지 않은데두요?
Even though I'm not.
그러니까 그렇게 보여야지
Because you're not.
임시 조립식 의족부터 시작해서
We'll start you off with a temporary prefab
차차 상황에 맞춰 조정해 나갈겁니다
and then make adjustments as we go.
이 친구 루디가 제몸을 원래대로
되돌려 놓을거예요, 새것처럼 좋게
Rudy here's gonna put back together again,good as new.
장애와 싸우는데는 마음가짐이 절반인데
아주 훌륭하네
Half the battle is attitude,
and you have a great one.
어쨋든 살아 있잖아
Well, I'm alive.
이런 일이 생길줄은 몰랐지만
여기 이렇게 살아 있으니까요
I didn't see that happening,but here I am.
어이, 꽃미남 양
나보다 먼저 작업거는 거야?
Yo, pretty boy,you're stealing my thunder,
이 섹시녀께서는 날 기다리고 있으니...
and I got a hottie waiting on me, so...
글쎄
I don't know.
이 분을 놓고 나랑
싸워야 될지도 모르지
I just might have to fight you for this one.
그래, 다음에 팔씨름으로 결판짓기로 하고
Okay,we'll arm-wrestle later.
이젠 그만 꺼져 주시지
Now get out of here.
이 친구 조심하세요
Watch out for this guy.
짐승이거든요
He's a dog.
실례하겠습니다
Excuse me.
저한테서 뭘 원하는지 알지만
많이 보진 못했어요
I know what you need, guys,but I didn't see much.
사소한 거 하나라도 저희에겐
도움이 될겁니다, 투치 씨
Well, any detail will help,mr. Tucci.
보자..그 놈은 제 뒤쪽에서 접근했어요
Well...he came up on me from behind,
그리고 마스크를 쓰고 있었어요
그때 말이에요..내 손을...
and he wore a mask when he made me put the...
아이스하키 할때 쓰는 마스크였어요
the...things on the ice.
제가 해드릴께요
I'll get it.
따뜻한 분이시군요
완전 천사표인거 아니에요?
Angel of mercy.
Just how merciful are you?
오, 정말 짐승이시네요, 네?
Oh, you are a dog,aren't you?
여자들은 그렇게 부르죠
So the ladies tell me.
범인의 키가 어느정도인지 아니면
흑인, 백인, 라틴계 어느쪽인지는요?
Can you tell us how tall he was or
if he was black,white, latino?
백인인거 같아요
White, I think.
아마... 키는 보통이었던거 같고
I'm guessing maybe average height --
뚱뚱하지도 마르지도 않은
보통 체격인가, 모르겠어요
not fat, not thin,just average.
I don't know.
그리고 그놈이 저한테 그..
작업할 때
And when he started, you know,working on me,
눈가리개를 하고 있어서...
I was blindfolded, so...
들으신 건 없나요?
did u hear anything?
말할때 억양 이나 아님 다른거라도?
Did he have an accent or anything?
그놈은 말을 많이 안했어요
해도 속삭이듯 했구요
He didn't talk much,or he'd whisper.
다른 소리는 들은게 없구요?
And that's all you heard?
쥐 소리요
Except the rats.
간혹 그놈들이 침대 위로 기어올라 와서
Sometimes they would crawl up on the bed,
흔들어서 떼어내야 했어요
and I'd have to shake them off.
참 쓸모없는 증인이죠, 네?
Some crap-ass witness I am, huh?
잘하고 계신 겁니다
많은 정보를 주셨어요
You're doing fine.
You've given us a lot.
그래요?
Yeah?
네
Yeah.
저기, 가끔 뭔가를 떠올리려고 노력할때
You know, sometimes when I'm trying to remember something
전 눈을 감아요
I close my eyes.
정말요?
Really?
당신에게도 다시 눈가리개를
해 드릴수 있는걸요
We could even blindfold you again.
제가 좀 피곤한거 같아요
...I'm kind of tired right now.
괜찮습니다, 좀 쉬세요
It's okay.Get some rest.
모건 경관과 전 가보겠습니다
Officer morgan and i are leaving.
혼자
Alone.
가식 없이
No pretending.
숨김도 없이
No hiding.
쉴 시간이 없다
No time to relax.
너무 가깝게 와 버렸다
I'm too close.
호르헤 카스티요는 나쁜 놈이다
Jorge castillo is bad.
그건 안다
That I know.
하지만 옐리나의 약혼자를
죽였을 만큼 나쁜 놈일까?
But bad enough to have killed yelina's fianc?
그건 내가 증명해야 한다
That I have to prove.
소박하지만은 않은 호르헤의 집
Jorge's not-so-humble abode.
이크, 돈 좀 벌었나보다
Yeesh -- new money.
평범한 사람들은 저런 걸 꿈꾼다
새 차, 큰 집
Normal people dream of this --a new car, a big home,
해변 모래사장 정박소의 보트...
a boat at the reef shore marina...
그리고 아름다운 아내
...and a beautiful wife.
곤란하게 됐다, 한번도 누군가를
과부로 만들어 본적은 없었는데
Too bad -- I never enjoy making someone a widow.
무척 행복해 보인다
They're so happy.
그녀는 어떤놈과 함께 있는지
전혀 모르고 있다
She has no clue who she's with.
어쩌면 그게 성공적인 남녀관계의
비결인지도 모른다
Maybe that's the secret to a successful relationship.
페리 씨, 당신은 투치 씨가 발견된
그 병원 마당에 있었습니다
Mr. Perry,you were on the grounds
of the same hospital where we found mr. Tucci.
그날밤 거기 혼자 있었습니까?
And you were alone that night?
어, 저하고 제 개 시저 뿐이었어요
Uh, it was just me and caesar, my dog.
시저가 버려진 빌딩을 좋아해요
쥐잡는 개거든요
He likes abandoned buildings.Caesar's a ratter.
이 사람은 무슨 짓을 저질렀죠?
What did this guy do?
왜요? 낯이 익은가요?
Why?Does he look familiar?
네, 이 사람, 그..존 싱글턴 영화에
나오는 배우랑 닮았어요
Yes, he looks like an actor from that john singleton movie.
제목이 뭐였죠?
What was that?
그 사람이 그 날밤 병원에서 본 사람인지
아닌지에나 집중하는게 어때요, 페리 씨?
How about you focus on whether or not he was thman
you saw at the old hospital that night, mr. Perry?
정확하게 말씀드리기는 어렵네요
Well, it was difficult to tell.
어두웠거든요
It was dark.
그 놈을 봤다고 하지 않았나요
You said you got a look at him.
모자를 쓰고 있었어요
He had a cap.
근데, 저거 디지탈 CCTV 네트워크로
연결되는 KG-230 인가요?
Hey, is that kg-230 hooked into a digital cctb network?
아주 튼튼한 방화벽이 필요하겠네요
KG-440을 쓰는게 더 낫긴 하겠지만
Ooh, you better have a hell of a firewall.
You get better resolution with the 440.
안녕하세요
Hello.
더 볼 것도 없군
We're done here.
잠시만 기다리세요
Give me a minute.
모건, 페리 씨한테 헛소리
고맙다고 전하고, 돌려 보내
Morgan, thank mr. Perry for his horseshit and send him home.
젠장할, 그 사람이 뭔가를
알려 줄지도 모르잖아요
Christ on a crutch,he could tell us something.
여기 독스 경사는
그사람 경찰서 구경온거 같다는데
Sergeant doakes says he is a looky-loo.
목격자 진술이 뉴스에 날 때마다
목격자랍시고 찾아오는 사람이 한 다스야
We get dozens like that every time a story hits the news.
그러니 부탁이야, 그 사람
우리 서에서 내쫓아 줘, 고마워
Now do me a favor --get him out of my precinct.Thank you.
좀 더 긍정적이 되도록 노력하셔야겠네요
You could try being a little more optimistic.
피해자인 토니 투치도 그렇게 긍정적인데
왜 우리는 긍정적일수 없냐구요
I mean, if tony tucci can be optimistic,I think we can.
목격자들이 정보를 더 줄껄요
You might get more out of people.
페리가 아무것도 모른다고
어떻게 확신하세요?
How do you know perry doesn't know anything?
왜냐면 내가 너보다
이 짓을 더 오래 해왔으니까
Because I've been doing this a lot longer than you.
좋아요
Okay.
니가 페리같은 머저리와 시간을 낭비하는
매 순간마다 사건은 미제가 돼가고 있어
This case is getting colder every minute
you waste on bullshit like perry.
그리고 충격받은 피해자한테
눈가리개를 씌운다구?
And wanting to blindfold a trauma victim?
도대체 씨발 무슨 생각으로 그런거야?
What the fuck were you thinking?
이제 투치는 입을 안 열거고
네가 투치 입을 막은거야
Tucci's closed for business now,and you shut him down.
전.. 새로운 접근법을 시도했던 거예요
I...I was trying a new approach.
쓸데없는 일에 시간낭비하기 전에
기초적인 것들부터 배워야 할껄
Maybe you should just learn the basics
before you reinvent the damn wheel.
나와요
어떻게 이런 음악에 춤을 안 춰요?
come on.How can you not dance to this?
이것도 재능이죠
It's a gift.
술이 좀 덜 들어간거 같지? 친구
We just need some more patrn, compadre.
한잔씩 더!
Another round!
난 됐어요
No more for me.
난 일찍 일어나야 해요
살인자들 잡아야죠
I got to get up early --killers to catch.
잊어버리라구
Forget that.
밤은 이제 시작이잖아
안 그래, 숙녀분들?
The night's just beginning,right, ladies?
그럼요!
Yes!
숙녀분들 잠시만요, 앤젤 이리와요
Ladies, excuse us.Angel, come here.
당신 부인이.. 걱정할 거예요
Your wife --she's probably worrying.
저 여자들 만난거 알면
어떨지 궁금하네요
I don't know what she'd think of your new friend.
집사람은 내가 누구랑 시시덕거리던
신경 안써, 내가 열정을 보여주는 한은
She don't mind who I flirt with as long
as I bring home la pasion.
열정이요?
La pasion?
그래, 열정이 남녀사이를
생기있게 해 주지
Yeah, it keeps the relationship alive.
커뮤니케이션이나 신뢰는 어떡해야 돼요?
Hey, what about, uh, communication, trust?
열정이면 돼
La pasion.
잠깐만요
Wait.
만약 여자가 뭔가를 더 원하면요?
What if she wants something more?
그럼 피스톤운동 좀 하는거지, 알잖아
Then you reciprocate --you know...
아뇨, 내말은
감정적으로 뭔가를 더 원할때요
no, I meant what if she wants something more emotionally?
감정적인 쪽으로는 가지마
Don't go down that emotional road.
그냥 육체 쪽으로만 가
Just go down on her.
쉬워, 여자가 더 열중할 껄
It's easier,and she'll be distracted.
이리와서 춤춰요, 앤젤
Come on.Let's dance, angel.
자...
So...
이제 뭐 하고 싶어요?
what do you want to do now?
그녀와 춤추거라, 덱스터
Dance with her, dexter.
정중하게 행동하고
Be polite.
펀치(음료)를 가져다 주고
Get her punch.
문을 열어주거라
Open the door for her.
그 애와 단둘이 있게 되고
And if you find yourself alone with her
분위기가 로맨틱해 지면..
and things get romantic --
아빠, 저 여자애랑 키스해 봤어요
dad, I've kissed a girl before.
그랬니?
You have?
네
Yeah.
그래서?
And?
글쎄요
I don't know.
괜찮았어요
It was okay.
덱스터, 여자들은 남자들과 다르단다
Dexter, women are different from men.
이런얘기 전에도 했었잖아요, 아빠
We've had this talk, dad.
여자들은 사물을 남자들과는
전혀 다른 식으로 경험한단다
I'm saying they have a whole different experience of things.
여자들은 누군가와 함께 있으면
신체적으로 연결돼 있다고 느끼고
When they're with someone,physically,they feel connected.
니가 그렇게 못 느낀다면 알아챌거야
니가 너무 노출돼 있기 때문이지
And they know when you're not.
They can sense it because you're very exposed.
그렇죠, 옷 벗고 있을테니
Yeah, you're naked.
감정적으로 그렇다는 말이다
I mean emotionally.
아들아, 이 문제는 너한테
아주 위험할 수도 있다
Son, this is going to be very dangerous for you.
속일 수 있어요
I can fake it.
많은 것들을 속이는 방법을
배울 수 있지만
Buddy, you can learn to fake a lot of things.
이번은 쉽지 않을거야
This is a tough one.
여기예요?
Is this it?
앤젤, 나 여기 딱 한번 와봤어요
기억이 안 난다구요
Angel, I've only been here one time.I don't remember.
일어나요
Wake up.
선배 부인이 날 아주 좋아하겠군요
Your wife's gonna love me.
평범함을 연기할때의 문제는 평범한 사람들이
이런 짜증나는 상황에 처한다는 것이다
The problem with acting normal is normal people
get into stupid situations like this.
오, 깜짝 놀랐잖아요
Oh. You scared the hell out of me.
미안해요, 니나
Sorry, nina.
전 덱스터라고 해요
I'm dexter.
기억나요?
저, 서에서 앤젤과 같이 일하잖아요
You remember?I work with angel down at the station.
여긴 왜 오셨는데요?
What are you doing here?
좀 웃겨요
It's funny.
우린 밖에서 앤젤이 봉급 오른걸
축하하고 있었어요
We were out celebrating angel's pay-grade bump.
봉급이 올랐다구요?
He got a raise?
네
Yeah.
음, 보시다시피, 어
너무 많이 마셨죠
Well, as you can see,he, uh, had a little too much to drink,
그래서 제가 데리고 온겁니다
so I gave him a ride home.
이 사람 이제 여기 안 살아요
He doesn't live here anymore.
오
Oh.
별거 중이에요
We're separated.
오우
Oh.
그럼...잘 가세요
So...good night.
아, 알겠습니다
Oh, okay.
안녕히 계세요
Good night.
일어나요
Come on.
그놈의 열정
La pasion.
앤젤
Angel.
앤젤, 우리 진짜로 지각하겠어요
Angel, we're really late for work, amigo.
아무래도 너무 많이 마셨나봐
I guess I had one too many, huh?
그러고 나서도
10잔 쯤을 더 마셨으니까요
And then about 10 more.
내가 여긴 어떻게 왔지?
How did I end up here?
기억 안나요?
You don't remember?
니가 여기 사는구나, 응?
So you live here, huh?
여기 살죠
I live here.
너 깔끔떠는 스타일이구나, 어?
You're kind of neat,aren't you?
엄마한테서 배운 나쁜 버릇이죠
Bad habit instilled by mom.
저기요
Hey.
출발하는게 좋겠어요
We better get going.
냉동 트럭 킬러때문에 비상이잖아요
Pressure's on with this ice-truck-killer situation.
그래, 너 먼저 가
Yeah. You go ahead.
내가 문 잠그고 나갈께
어차피 집에도 들러야 하니까
I'll lock up.
I have to stop by home anyway.
집사람이 걱정할거야
My wife's gonna be worried.
화내면서 바가지나 긁겠지, 알잖아
She gets so hot and bothered.
No, I'll just wait,and I'll drop you at your car.
아뇨, 기다렸다가
선배 차 있는데까지 태워다 줄께요
화장실은 어디지?
Where's your bathroom?
평범해 보이려는 사람이 나 혼자가
아니라는걸 알때면 어쩐지 위안이 된다
Somehow it's reassuring to know I'm not
the only one pretending to be normal.
여기서 털을 하나 찾았는데
투치 털은 아냐
I found hair on this one that doesn't
belong to tucci --rat hair.
쥐털이야
쥐털땜에 나 아무래도 기생충에 감염...
I probably picked up a parasite just --
나 시험하지마, 마수카
don't test me, masuka.
여기 찢겨져 나간거 보이죠?
Uh, you see all that shredding?
침대보 절반은 쥐 둥지에 있을 거예요
Half of this sheet must be lining their nests.
쥐들이 범죄현장에서
증거물을 가져갔다고?
They took evidence away from the crime scene?
그렇죠
Exactly.
그럼 가서 둥지를 확인해야지
So we check their nest.
어...찾는게 뭔지 모르는 채로는
뜬구름 잡는 식이 될거예요
Uh...wild goose chase,without knowing
what we're looking for.
투치와 다시 얘기해봐야 돼요
We could talk to tucci again.
투치는 생각보다 많은걸 알거고
제 직감으론 다시 입을 열거예요
He knows more than he thinks,
and my gut tells me he can take it.
그래, 너 직감하난 베테랑 급이지
'Cause you got the instincts of a veteran on the force.
마수카, 침대보 검사해
Masuka, run the sheet.
제조회사를 찾을 수 있겠는지 알아봐
See if we can trace it to manufacturer.
난 법정에 가봐야 돼
그러니까 연락은 내 휴대폰으로...
I've got court in the morning,so call me on my cell --
좋아요, 알아요, 저 신참이에요
all right, I get it.I'm a newbie.
하지만, 선배는 늙고 지쳤고
이걸 새로운 시각으로 봐야해요
But you are old and tired,and you need new eyes on this.
그러니까, 내 일을 하게
날 내버려 둘 준비가 되면, 알려 주세요
So when you're ready to let me do my job, you let me know.
빌어먹을 입도 뻥긋하지마, 마수카
And don't you fucking say a word, masuka.
돈 못낸 사람들을
어떻게 제거했지, 호르헤?
How do you get rid of the ones who don't pay out?
바다 한가운데에다 그들을 던졌나,
Do you drop them in the middle of the ocean,
육지로 헤엄쳐 가라고 말하면서?
tell them to swim for shore?
오래 숨어있진 못할꺼다, 호르헤
You can't hide for long, jorge.
여보세요
Hello?
덱스터, 나야
Dexter, it's me.
저기, 거기서 본 이후로
연락 안한 거 미안해
Look, I'm sorry I haven't talked to you since that place.
시체 공시소 말이구나
The morgue.
경찰에서 범인을 잡을 수 있을거 같아?
Do you think they'll be able to catch whoever did this?
분명 그 놈은 마땅한 댓가를 치를거야
I'm sure he'll get what he deserves.
어떻게 지내?
How are you doing?
아직도 좀 떨려
Still a little shaky.
심야작업 해야할게 좀 있긴 하지만
I have some late-night work I have to do,
그전에 들를 수 있어
니가 원한다면
but I could stop by earlier,if you want.
영화 빌려보는 것도 괜찮겠다
Maybe we could rent a movie.
그래, 내가 DVD 빌려갈께
좀 가벼운 걸로
Yeah, I'll pick up a dvd --something light.
눈을 깜박이지 않고 있으면
눈물이 흐를까
Maybe if I don't blink,my eyes will tear up.
정말 싫다
I hate this.
난 행동 하나하나를 신경쓰고 있다
정말 지친다
I'm questioning every move.It's exhausting.
신경쓰길 그만뒀어야 했다
I should just break it off already,
리타를 달래 줄수 없고
뭔가...를 해줄수 없다면 말이다
unless I can pacify her,give her...something,reciprocate.
피스톤운동 같은
열정!
La pasion.
워우, 어, 덱스터?
Whoa, uh, dexter?
미안해
I'm sorry.
난, 어...
I-I, uh...
오, 난 그냥...
oh, I was just...
당신이 나한테 너무 잘해줘서
you were so generous with me.
보답을 하려던 거지
I was gonna return the favor.
오, 정말 듣기좋은 말이지만, 미안해
Oh, no, that's very sweet,but I'm sorry.
그냥, 그럴 기분이 아니라서
I'm just not in the mood for that.
덱스터냐?
That you, dex?
네, 늦어서 죄송해요
Yeah.Sorry I'm late.
괜찮다, 아들아
It's okay, son.
늦었으니 재미있게 놀았겠구나
You must have been having fun.
그런 척 했어요
I pretended to.
잘했다, 얘야
That's good, dexter.
아빠?
Dad?
언젠가는 저도 그걸 진짜로
느낄수 있을까요?
Do you think that maybe one day I'll feel it for real?
그랬으면 좋겠구나
I hope so, son.
정말로
I really do.
혼자, 떨어져 있는 편이 낫다
Alone, I'd be better off.
남녀관계는 너무 복잡미묘하다
Relationships are too confusing.
하지만 이건 이해가 가능하다
But this I can figure out.
내가 잘하는 이것
This I do well.
호르헤 카스티요의 보트다
Jorge castillo's boat.
그가 살인을 했다면, 증거가 있을 것이다
If he's a killer,then there's proof.
항상 증거는 있는 법이고
내가 찾아낼 것이다
There's always proof,and I'll find it.
행복하고 사랑에 빠진...
완벽한 커플
Happy, in love...the perfect couple.
리타와 아이들도
낚시를 좋아할지 궁금하다
I wonder if rita and the kids would like fishing.
집중하자
Focus.
이 중 하나가 어네스토를 데려온
코요테의 전화번호와 일치한다면
If one of these matches the contact number for ernesto's coyote,
니가 그 코요테인거지, 호르헤
you're it, jorge.
밀입국자들을 여기서 익사시킨후
바다 멀리 나가서 버린다면
He drowns them here,then dumps them out there.
해변으로 시체가 떠밀려와도
또 하나의 튜브 사고로만 기록되겠지
If they wash up,it'll be chalked up
to another inner-tube mishap.
그래, 이건 내가 잘하지
Yep -- this I do well.
그 놈 신발을 떠올려 보세요
Think about his shoes.
절둑거리면서 걸었는지
Did he walk with a limp?
운동선수처럼 쉽게 잘 걸었는지
Did he move smoothly,like an athlete?
기억하려고 애써 보세요, 토니
절 위해서
Try to remember, tony,for me.
할수 있다면 하죠
I would if I could, hon.
당신은 매력적인 사람이에요
나한테 그 매력을 이용할 만큼 영리하구요
You're a sweet lady,and smart
using your charms on me.
아니에요, 전 신경 안써요
No, no, I don't mind.
아마 여자랑 이렇게 바라보면서
수다떠는 것도 마지막일 테니까요
It's probably the last time a woman
will flirt with me,looking like this.
괜찮아요, 토니
It's okay, tony.
나중에도 할수 있을거예요
Maybe later.
눈가리개를 써봅시다
We should try the blindfold.
뭐라구요?
What?
그건 하고 싶지 않은데요
I don't want to do that.
죄송합니다만, 투치 씨
I'm sorry, mr. Tucci.
당신이 겪은 일을
저는 감히 상상도 할수 없지만
I can't even begin to imagine what you've been through
또 다른 누군가가 그런 일을
겪지 않게 해야하는게 저희 일입니다
but it's our job to make sure
that nobody else goes through it, too.
그러니 모건, 시작해도 돼
So, morgan, you're up.
그놈은 소리를 거의 안 냈어요
He was hard to hear.
그 놈이 어디 있는지 전혀 몰랐으니까요
I never knew where he was.
그럼 행동이 민첩한 놈이군요
잘했어요, 토니
So he's agile.That's good, tony.
또 들은 건요?
What else did you hear?
쥐들이요
Rats.
항상 망할놈의 쥐들이 있었어요
Always those damn rats.
그 놈한테 집중해요, 토니
Try to focus on him, tony.
뭘 들었어요?
What did you hear?
냄새는 나지 않았나요?
What did you smell?
박하냄새가 났어요
Menthol.
박하냄새요?
Menthol?
네 목캔디 냄새같았어요
Yeah, like cough drops.
놈은 기침을 많이 했어요
He cleared his throat a lot.
아시죠, 이런...
You know, like --
놈이 포장지를 벗겼어요
He unwrapped them.
부스럭거리는 포장지 소리를
들을 수 있었어요
I could hear those wrappers,that crinkly sound.
그리고는 입에 넣고 빨았어요
And he sucked on them.
이빨에 부딪혀서 달그락거리는
소리를 들었어요, 그때가 놈이 내...
I could hear them clicking against his teeth when he...
그 개자식은 그 망할놈의
목캔디를 좋아했어요
The son of a bitch loved those fucking lozenges.
이 둥지엔 아무것도 없어
Nothing in this nest.
다른 층을 살펴보자
이놈들 건물 전체에 퍼져 있으니까
Well, check another floor.They're all over this dump.
에이 제기랄
Fuck this.
마수카
Masuka.
여기 둥지가 또 있어
We got another one over here.
기대해도 되겠어
침대보 조각이 몇개 있네
Promising.Several fragments from the sheet here.
쥐새끼들이 우리한텐
아주 단골 손님이구만
These rat bastards were repeat customers.
누가 점심에 마늘 먹었어?
Who had garlic for lunch?
니 목덜미에 한방 먹이는 수가 있어
I'm gonna punch you in the neck.
내 생각엔...
뽀뽀를 해줘도 모자랄거 같은데
Actually...I think you're gonna french me.
...2934.
내가 옮을 때가 좋다
I like being right.
대개는 내가 옳다, 이쪽 일에 관해선
I usually am,about these things.
"준비되어 있어라", 내 모토다
"Be prepared" -- my motto.
보이스카웃과 내가
공통으로 가지고 있는 것
The boy scouts and i have that in common.
물론, 오늘밤 외출로
'메리트 뱃지'를 받을 수는 없다
(보이스카웃에서 착한일을 하면 주는 뱃지)
Of course, there's no merit badge for tonight's outing.
뭘 보고 있는 거죠?
What are we looking at?
냉동트럭 살인마의 목캔디 포장지를
찾았어, 니 동생한테 감사해
They found the ice-truck killer's
lozenge wrapper,thanks to your sister.
목캔디 포장지?
Lozenge wrapper?
두달동안 허탕만 쳤으니, 목캔디 포장지
하나면 망할놈의 성배(聖杯)를 찾은거지
Hey, after two months of finding fuck all in this case,
a lozenge wrapper's the damn holy grail.
내 연쇄살인범 친구가 목캔디를 먹는다
My favorite serial killer is a lozenge eater.
얼마나 인간적인가
How human of him.
부분 지문이 나왔어
We have a partial.
부분 지문..
빌어먹을 부분 지문이라구요!
Partial print --a partial fucking print!
축하한다, 동생
Proud of you, sis.
오빠, 같이 축하해야지
Hey, it's a celebration here.
어디 가는 거야?
Where are you going?
범죄 현장
Crime scene.
좀 비켜 주세요
Excuse me.
어, 무슨...일이지?
What's, uh --what's going on?
방금 냉동트럭 킬러 사건의
첫번째 물증을 찾았습니다
We've got our first piece of tangible
evidence on the ice-truck killer.
빌어먹을 부분 지문이요
A partial fucking print.
지문검색시스템에 돌려봤어?
You run it through afis yet?
하고 있습니다 / 일치하는 사람만
나오면 나머진 일도 아니에요
It doesn't even matter if we get a match.
아무 이유로나 엮어서 체포만 하면 돼죠
He gets pulled in for something,anything, we got him.
지문 검색하기 전에 사진부터 찍어둬
We get it photoed before we scan it.
지문검색시스템과 대조할 지문 포인트를
부분 지문에서 확실하게 확보하고
마수카, 포장지에서
DNA 채취할수 있나 확인하고
그리고 그 병원 건물도
계속 수색합시다, 여러분
...And let's keep working the old hospital site, people.
또 운좋게 뭔가를 건질지도 모르니까
You never know.We might get lucky again.
운이 아니었어
It wasn't luck.
잘했어, 모건
Good work, morgan.
밖으로 나와, 어서
Afuera, va.
신속히들 움직여
Muevanse. Come on.
빨리!
Come on!
들어가, 들어가
Entrar, entrar.
미국을 축복하소서
God bless america.
여보?
Hon?
당신 어딨어요?
Where are you?
여보?
Honey?
당신 안에 있어?
Honey, you in here?
내 가족에게 보내줘요!
Iderrito a mi familia!
거기 쳐박혀 있어
이 빌어먹을 쿠바 쓰레기야!
Get back in there,you cuban piece of shit!
빌어먹을 짐승같은 것들
Fucking animals.
믿기지가 않는다
Incredible.
생각보다 훨씬 잘 어울리는 한쌍이다
They're an even better match than I thought --
진정한 협력관계
true partnership.
원래 계획에서 조금 빗나가긴 했지만
You know,I rarely deviate from a plan,
당신들을 헤어지게 하는건
마음이 아파서 말야, 이렇게...
but I just didn't have the heart to split up such A...
완벽한 커플인데
...Perfect couple.
당신들...
You two...
수입이 꽤 짭짤한 사업을 하고 있던데
have quite a lucrative operation going.
정말 훌륭한 팀이야
You're a really good team.
영리하기도 하지
It's clever, too.
익사체가 떠오른다고 해서, 누가
이상하게 생각하겠어, 쿠바 남자나 여자...
No one questions another drowned cuban man or woman...
아니면 아이...
or child.
이런 사업은 어느 쪽이 생각해 낸거야?
So, which one of you thought this up?
그 사람들 자유를 얻잖아요
They get freedom.
우리가 자유를 준다구요
We free them.
다들 우리한테 감사해요
정말이에요
They thank us,for god's sake.
익사시킨 다음 바다에 버려줘서 고맙대?
For drowning them and dumping
their bodies in the ocean?Please.
돈 드릴께요, 돈은 있어요
We can pay you.We have money.
무슨 일이든 돈 때문이야, 그렇지?
That's what it's all about, right?
사랑해
I love you.
정말 사랑해요
I love you so much.
너무너무 사랑해
질문을 하나 할꺼야
I'm gonna ask you a question.
솔직하게 대답해 줬음 좋겠어
I want you to answer me honestly.
더이상 헛소리 말고, 알아 들어?
No more bullshit.Do you understand?
결혼한 지는 얼마나 됐어?
How long have you been married?
5.. / 12년요
12 years.
어떻게 서로 사랑할 수 있는거지?
How do you love each other?
당신들은 나랑 비슷해
그런데도 사랑을 하잖아, 어떻게?
You're like me,and you make it work.How?
우린 원하는 삶이 같아요
We want the same life.
우린 둘다...
We both --
우린 같은 것들을 원하죠
we want the same thing.
같은 삶이요
Same life.
같은 꿈을 나눠 가진거군
You share the same dream.
그래요 정답이에요, 맞아요
Yes, exactly, yes.
맞아요, 바로 그거죠
Yes, that's it.
그건, 음...
That's, uh...
도움이 되는군
...helpful.
고마워
Thank you.
안돼
No.
나는 정확한 일처리를 좋아한다
하지만 시간이 없다
I like doing things properly,but I'm out of time,
이들을 마무리해야 한다
and I still have to dispose of them.
발레리를 급하게 대충 작업했다
Valerie got short shrift.
하지만 대체적으로는
상당히 만족스런 밤이었다
But all in all,it was a very good night.
난 이 곳이 좋다
I like this place.
많은 추억들이 저 아래에 묻혀있다
A lot of memories are buried down there.
계획에서 벗어난건
경솔한 짓이었는지도 모른다
Deviating from the plan may have been ill-advised.
하지만 때로는 위험도 감수해야 한다
But sometimes you just have to take a risk.
결국...
After all...
남녀사이도
위험을 감수해야만 한다는 것인가?
...isn't that what relationships are all about?
꿈 가진 거 있어?...
Do you have a dream...
일생에 있어서...
...for your life...
그러니깐 미래에?
your future, I guess?
물론이지
Of course.
당신은 있어?
Do you?
이상하게 들릴지도 몰라
It might sound weird.
난 언젠가는 만족스럽고 행복하고 싶어
I want to someday be content and just feel...
다른 사람들처럼 편안함을 느끼면서
comfortable,like everyone else.
그건...
I want...
평범한 삶이구나
a normal life.
그래, 평범한 삶
Yeah, a normal life.
그게 내가 원하는 거야
That's all I want.
바로 그거야
Just that.
부(富)도 명예도 전혀 없이
No fame and fortune --
작은 일에도 기뻐 날뛰면서?
excitement at every turn?
아니, 그건 충분히 느껴왔어
No, I've had enough excitement.
고마워
Thank you.
이젠...
Now...
지루한 쪽을 택할래
I'll take boring.
중간으로 해
Average.
보통으로
Ordinary.
그건 좀 이상하다, 응?
That's weird, huh?
그래
Yeah.
싱크 : YTET-Vicky8800
(www.ydy.com/bbs)
번역 : ck , DC 미드갤
Sync:YTET-Vicky8800
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-